In a future without water, vengeance will rain.
Young Ones is a western, action, drama film directed by Jake Paltrow.
In a future where water is scarce, a farmer defends his land
and hopes to rejuvenate his parched soil.
However, his daughter's boyfriend schemes to steal the land for himself.
Ernest Holm, played by Michael Shannon.
Flem Lever, played by Nicholas Hoult.
Mary Holm, played by Elle Fanning.
Jerome Holm, played by Kodi Smit-McPhee.
Katherine Holm, played by Aimee Mullins.
Robbie, played by Christy Pankhurst.
Young Ones (UK title Bad Land: Road to Fury) is a 2014 action science
fiction film directed and written by Jake Paltrow.
The film stars Nicholas Hoult, Elle Fanning,
Michael Shannon and Kodi Smit-McPhee.
The film had its world premiere at 2014 Sundance
Film Festival on 18 January 2014.
The film was released on 17 October 2014 in the United States.
The film explores themes of future, dystopia, rain, love, murder.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.